<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>n montano</title>
    <description>n montano
</description>
    <link>http://erikradio.github.io/</link>
    <!-- <atom:link href="http://erikradio.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/> -->
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 13:39:48 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 13:39:48 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jack Pine or Nash Redoak</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For the millionth time two postcards of disturbing art in his hand.    It was simple. You held on to them and when the horror (usually the one in
      the artwork) came from behind you just needed to show them the card. Otherwise, darkness.
      Death?    It was always after the first horror. He would lose the second
      card. Montano knew what would come and was no longer uneasy. It would happen again after
      all.    The skinny faceless man was coming.    Montano
      rested against the blue bricks of the dark chamber. Heltroy, either aware or also subject to
      the approaching horror sat down on his lap to face him. A moonlight spread across her breasts
      which were secured in a bra of ornate black pattern.    “Well,” said
      Montano. “Why not?”    He removed the bra to find another thin net
      beneath. Removed, another invisible bra of spider silk. Montano struggled to remove it all, to
      place his lips on her before the faceless man arrived.    Near the
      surface, the question of the name of the tree detective.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://erikradio.github.io/2015/10/Jack-Pine-or-Nash-Redoak</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://erikradio.github.io/2015/10/Jack-Pine-or-Nash-Redoak</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ham</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For the second time into the snow battered hotel, somewhere near the
      Nebraskan town Montano had seen before.    Cop walked up to the
      window.    ‘Now you didn’t meant to go past us like that did you?’    ‘No,’ said Montano, who had already been pulled over twice for
      speeding.    ‘Montano!!’ said the other cop, exiting his car, shirtless.
      He motioned to a nearby store. ‘Ice cream! Distilled!’    A dark room. Two
      large ham sandwiches, several feet long, prepared by a mother for Johnny.    ‘Oh yes,’ he said. ‘Never have I seen such wonderful asses such as these.’    Montano glanced over at the sandwiches which were nervously shaking. Live
      pigs between bread.    Johnny removed the bread from one and mounted it,
      thrusting aggressively into the orifice on the pig’s back. The pig squeaked anxiously.
      Johnny’s thrusting intensified and he began to pull back the skin of the pig as he came closer
      to climaxing, revealing the dripping BBQ flesh beneath.    Cops in the
      rear view mirror again.    Snow.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://erikradio.github.io/2015/08/Ham</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://erikradio.github.io/2015/08/Ham</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Corinth</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It was the pesticides that were turning people into zombies. The police
      were involved as well. Nobody believed Montano when he told them, and so he continued to
      escape from one apartment complex to the next trying to keep just ahead of the hordes. A debit
      card (Bill’s) flew in the wind.    An interlude with corinthian columns. A
      recently evacuated apartment. Fountains flowing, trash everywhere. Mixin bent over and when
      Montano had finished his first, he withdrew. She screamed, demanding he put on a new
             prophylactic. He threw the used one across the room, a
      slimy skin, an alien embryro.             He again tried to explain about the pesticides, but not even his
      parents would believe him.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://erikradio.github.io/2015/08/Corinth</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://erikradio.github.io/2015/08/Corinth</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Assman</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Upon entering the hotel room Kramer was shocked to find the marble dildo in
      the hand of the investigator. The latter buried himself under the sheets as Kramer grabbed
      them. He stepped out of the room and shut the door, began walking down the hall. Running now.
      The sheets stretching endlessly behind him towards the hotel room. Running. A long white
      banner stretching across the sand as Kramer made his way into the dark sea.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://erikradio.github.io/2015/07/Assman</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://erikradio.github.io/2015/07/Assman</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In Missouri</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Stopped on an interminable trip through/from Iowa (connotations of false
      Mason City emanate deep). Protestations regarding the need to stop, something sinister. A
      shack, rain falling, grime. A game cycling back on itself. Basements, darkness.    Her generous ass paraded around the room. The only chance for freedom. A
      green, glowing square situated very significantly on her lower left cheek. He grabbed the
      laser gun and fired. Her ass was quick but finally impact. Like an ancient column, the green
      square cracked slowly working its way into the flesh. Green light dims, extinguished. Gently a
      flower placed in a perfectly circular crater where the disintegrated ass had fallen
      away.    A suburban house’s garage where in front of a car’s trunk where a
      mother collapses to her knees dead as Wagnerian strings soar. With his foot Montano pushes the
      corpse underneath the car, then kicks the villain with a snide grin to the audience, the work
      ends on a note of glorious resignation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://erikradio.github.io/2015/06/In-Missouri</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://erikradio.github.io/2015/06/In-Missouri</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dreamtionary II</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Kresnophobia  : the fear of no smoke&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://erikradio.github.io/2015/03/Dreamtionary-II</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://erikradio.github.io/2015/03/Dreamtionary-II</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Failure and Flight</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The arrow gun fired into the heads of the three teenage girls. Two, a
      success. The third–why was she still alive? They began talking about their boyfriends, and
      Montano joined in the conversation briefly before catching up with his situation.    It was all fucked up. His comrades, so close to the highest level of the
      building, had run out of ammo. Now, rumblings below of the betrayed could be felt. They were
      trapped. It had been worth a shot, but there was no chance to succeed now. Death by firing
      squad.    He remembered the field of dogs. Looking up into the great
      expanse of sky, the giant blue nebula the animals worshipped pulsed. They stared utterly
      mesmerized. A stranger came to each of the dogs and removed their one glowing eye. Montano
      looked over at the pug, a companion of uncertain loyalties. A leaf was over his head.    ‘Do you still-“    ‘Shut up.’ The pug leaned down,
      exposing he still had his glow eye, his source of power.      The building. Montano and another middle aged woman in glasses raced down the stairs. A
      wrong turn into a room with a record player. Gunshots above where once they had all waltzed.
      Music began to play.      He remembered the seduction. Laying on
      a bench, chewing gum. Some children and their mother approached. He offered them gum. They
      returned soon after.    “Would you like to take a break,” began the
      mother.    “A break?”    “From the chewing.”    Montano caught the euphemism. He made it to their house. She was an enemy. He
      ran. But now he knew how to enter the tower.      Down the
      endless stairs.      And it’s time, time, time…      They put their shoes on. Montano slipped his atomic white sneakers onto his
      feet. The woman froze. ‘I love this song…” They sang along.  &lt;br /&gt;
            And it’s time, time, time…      Into the street. The woman was gone. Do i need this salt jacket anymore?           And it’s time, time, time that you
      love  …    The street. A mass of people. Passport to Mexico. Was
      he married? He slipped into the crowd.      And it’s time, time,
      time…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://erikradio.github.io/2015/01/Failure-and-Flight</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://erikradio.github.io/2015/01/Failure-and-Flight</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Strange Trash</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Clean, metallic, industrial. The walls segmented into numerous rectangles.
      Montano looked down on the shiny, immaculately clean floor beneath him impressed.    The cleaners arrived with brooms in hand. A loud whirring emanated from
      everywhere in the facility. The cleaning had begun.    The rectangles on
      the wall began to vibrate back and forth, emitting bursts of hot air that pushed the trash on
      the floor in one direction, only to be repositioned by air from another delivered precisely at
      the correct interval. From there the cleaners would push their brooms onto the trash, wittling
      away at it until it had disappeared.    Montano had trouble battling the
      wind blasting around him, but remained upright. A small puddle of trash, brown and metallic
      formed near his feet.    ‘This is always a tough one,’ said a cleaner.
      ‘All that krampus!’    He was joined by other cleaners who together pushed
      their brooms into the trash. It was resistant and by the prolonged effort of the cleaners
      Montano could see why it required all of their efforts to remove it.    The trash, focusing in on a microscopic level, was made of many artifacts of the past
      day. Montano had no difficulty dissecting it into smaller and smaller pieces with his knife to
      aid in the cleaning process. But then he stopped as he noticed what was in the middle of the
      trash.    The Animal, now in the form of a cougar, sat there looking at
      Montano with trusting eyes. The same animal that Montano had saved from the flood house and
      who had been his companion. It had to be removed. Montano slowly inserted his knife vertically
      into the creature. Tears streamed from his eyes and onto the trash as he began to quarter the
      beast.    “Will someone else…”    Nobody would. He
      continued to dismember the cougar, who looked up at him with accepting, loving, and
      understanding eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2015 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://erikradio.github.io/2015/01/Strange-Trash</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://erikradio.github.io/2015/01/Strange-Trash</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Untitled VII</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The wall-less house had succeeded in fending off the zombie hoard who, as
      they exited the building across the street, looked on the house with horror knowing that they
      stood no chance against the fierce living warriors inside.    “Another,”
      pointed Montano. A blue faced man with tentacled pinto beans crawling across his maroon suit
      appeared in a window. “No,” said somebody, “that just signals the end of the movie.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://erikradio.github.io/2014/11/Untitled-VII</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://erikradio.github.io/2014/11/Untitled-VII</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>act i szene 2</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Against a red wall.    Bond leaped onto the back of the
      japanese man, shoving a pill into his mouth in the process. He grabbed his neck, forcing the
      pill down through a repeated downward gesture on the man’s throat. his face began to turn
      purple as nearby in the auditorium    Montano made his way though a large,
      rustling crowd of italian mobsters to find his seat next to jack. a man in plaid with a
      prominent gut took the stage (this was a different stage from the one the mobsters were
      watching but weren’t there anymore) and began preaching about      karbara  : (in sultry tone, omnipresent)
      …  nice…        plaid:   what?     karbara: …  nice…        plaid  : what? what?           karbara:   …  nice…      (montano
      and jack exchange blank glances indicating slight confusion)      plaid  : what? what what            karbara  :…  nice…        plaid  : whatwhatwhatwhatwhatwhatwhatwha    karbara:
      …  nice…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://erikradio.github.io/2014/09/act-i-szene-2</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://erikradio.github.io/2014/09/act-i-szene-2</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
